Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
Montana Attorney General's Office Records
1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
RS 76
Montana Attorney General's Office
199 linear feet of shelf space
These records of the Montana Attorney General's Office consist of general correspondence (1905-1920); subject files (1900-1962); informal opinions (1897-1915); docket registers (1893-1963); docketed and undocketed case files (1902-1968); financial ledgers (1905-1969); and an abstract register (1921-1941). (RESTRICTION: Permission of State Archivist is required for use of folder 41 in Box 96)
The Montana Attorney General was originally authorized under the Organic Act of 1864 which established Montana as a territory. The 1889 Constitution established the office as an elective executive office. The duties of the Attorney General included prosecuting and defending all cases to which the State or any county was a party; enforcing judgements reached in such cases; supervising county attorneys; giving opinions on legal issues to state agencies, the legislature, and county officials; to bid on property in the name of the state; and to serve ex officio on a variety of boards and commissions including the Board of Examiners, the Board of Land Commissioners, the Board of Education, the Board of Equalization, the Board of State Prison Commissioners, the Board of Pardons, and others. While the specifics of the duties have changed over the years, the general principal that the Attorney General is the attorney for the state, has remained constant. As the complexities of state government have increased the Attorney General has acquired a staff of Assistant Attorneys General to handle most of the work. Many of these are assigned to specific agencies. Among the Attorneys General during the period of these records were Albert J. Galen (1905-1913), S.C. Ford (1917-1921), L.A. Foot (1924-1933), Harrison J. Freeborn (1937-1941), R.V. Bottomly (1942-1949), Arnold Olsen (1949-1957), and Forrest Anderson (1957- ).
Records consist of general correspondence (1905-1920); subject files (1901-1962, includes name index 1947-1962); informal opinions (1897-1915); docket registers (1893-1963); dockets (1912-1966); land dockets (1902-1912); undocketed cases (1903-1968); financial ledgers (1905-1969); and an land abstract register (1921-1941).
The collection is arranged by series.
Collection open for research.
Acquisition information is available upon request.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Banks and Banking--Montana; African Americans--Montana; Consumer Protection; Political corruption--Montana; County attorneys--Montana; Education finance; Electric Power; Environmental Policy; Gambling; Insurance companies; Labor disputes; Law enforcement; Liquor industry; Liquor laws; Local government--Montana; Municipal government--Montana; Petroleum industry and trade--Montana; Prisons--Montana; Prostitution--Montana; Public utilities----Montana; Railroads--Montana; Salish Indians--government Relations; Train robberies; World War, 1914-1918--Enemy aliens--Montana; Grazing leases--Montana
Government and politics; Agriculture; Montana
Detailed Description of the Collection
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection
- General Correspondence
  - A-L, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 1-25)
  - M-Z, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 2 / 1-24)
  - Attorney Generals, 1908-1917 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
  - A-Z, 1908-1916 (Box-folder 3 / 2)
  - A-Z, 1917 (Box-folder 3 / 3)
  - A-Z, 1918 (Box-folder 3 / 4-23)
  - A-Y, 1919 (Box-folder 4 / 1-19)
  - A-Y, 1920 (Box-folder 4 / 20-38)
- Subject Files
  - Abatement, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5 / 1)
  - Abstracts, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5 / 2-3)
  - Admission to the Bar, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 5 / 4-9)
  - Agricultural College, 1914-1918 (Box-folder 5 / 10)
  - Animals, Range, Care of, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 5 / 11)
  - Anonymous letters, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 5 / 12)
  - Appointments: Agricultural College to Child Protection Bureau, 1902-1907 (Box-folder 5 / 13)
  - Appointments: Coal Mine Inspector, 1900-1905 (Box-folder 5 / 14-16)
  - Appointments: Consolidated Boards Clerk to Humane Society Board, 1901-1907 (Box-folder 5 / 17-18)
  - Appointments: Judicial District judges (2nd, rth, 9th, 13th), 1901-1907 (Box-folder 5 / 19-30)
  - Appointments: Land Commission Clerk to World's Fair Commission, miscellaneous), 1901-1907 (Box-folder 5 / 31-33)
  - Appointments: Boiler Inspector to Engineer, 1908-1917 (Box-folder 5 / 34-37)
  - Appointments: Judicial District judges (4th), 1911 (Box-folder 5 / 38-39)
  - Appointments: Judicial District judges (6th, 8th, 10th, 12th, 13th), 1909-1912 (Box-folder 6 / 1-9)
  - Appointments: Secretary of State to Veterinarian; miscellaneous, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 6 / 10-17)
  - Appropriations, 1910-1920 (Box-folder 6 / 18)
  - Arnoldy case, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 6 / 19)
  - Assessment, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 6 / 20)
  - Assignments, 1919 (Box-folder 6 / 21)
  - Automobiles, 1913-1921 (Box-folder 6 / 22)
  - Bailey vs. Fox, 1928 (Box-folder 6 / 23)
  - Banking laws, 1907-1920 (Box-folder 6 / 24)
  - Bank receiverships, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 6 / 25-26)
  - Josiah F. Beck estate, 1910-1912 (Box-folder 6 / 27)
  - Blue Sky Law, 1915-1920 (Box-folder 6 / 28-29)
  - Boards (miscellaneous), 1908-1910 (Box-folder 6 / 30)
  - Bond issues, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 6 / 31)
  - Bonds, 1908-1912 (Box-folder 6 / 32-33)
  - Bonds, 1917-1921 (Box-folder 7 / 1-2)
  - Boulder explosion, 1910 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
  - Bounty claims, 1909-1910, 1915-1918 (Box-folder 7 / 4)
  - Bridges, 1910-1920 (Box-folder 7 / 5)
  - Butte election fraud case, 1918 (Box-folder 7 / 6-8)
  - Butte gambling cases, 1927 (Box-folder 7 / 9-10)
  - Butte liquor abatement, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 7 / 11)
  - Capitol Building, 1909-1917 (Box-folder 7 / 12-17)
  - Certificates, 1910-1915 (Box-folder 7 / 18)
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad vs. Ross, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 7 / 19)
  - Children, 1915-1920 (Box-folder 7 / 20)
  - Chinese lottery, 1918 (Box-folder 7 / 21)
  - Chiropractors' law, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 7 / 22)
  - Cities and towns, requests from, 1908-1909, 1916-1920 (Box-folder 7 / 23-25)
  - Citizenship, 1907-1914 (Box-folder 7 / 26)
  - City officers, 1908-1910 (Box-folder 7 / 27)
  - Civil cases, 1908-1911 (Box-folder 7 / 28-29)
  - Civil cases, 1912-1920 (Box-folder 8 / 1-7)
  - Claims, 1914-1921 (Box-folder 8 / 8-9)
  - R.L Clinton file, 1919 (Box-folder 8 / 10)
  - Coal lands, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 8 / 11)
  - Charles Colbert estate, 1911-1917 (Box-folder 8 / 12)
  - Collections, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 8 / 13)
  - Collections: Land Dept., 1910-1915 (Box-folder 8 / 14)
  - Commutation of sentence, 1910-1917 (Box-folder 8 / 15)
  - Compensation, 1916-1920 (Box-folder 8 / 16-17)
  - Complaints, 1908-1912 (Box-folder 8 / 18-22)
  - Complaints, 1913-1920 (Box-folder 9 / 1-19)
  - Contracts, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 10 / 1)
  - Coroners' fees, 1908-1916 (Box-folder 10 / 2)
  - Corporations, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 10 / 3-4)
  - Corrupt Practices Act, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 10 / 5)
  - Counties, 1907-1920 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
  - County Assessors, 1911-1919 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
  - County Attorneys, 1910-1921 (Box-folder 10 / 8-11)
  - County Commissioners, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 10 / 12-13)
  - Criminal cases, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 10 / 14-17)
  - Deputies, 1911-1920 (Box-folder 10 / 18)
  - Dinky Caboose Law, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 10 / 19)
  - Disbarment, 1908-1920, 1925 (Box-folder 11 / 1-3)
  - District courts, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
  - District judges, 1913-1918 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
  - Districts (joint, herd, school, etc.), 1918-1920 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
  - Divorce, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
  - Drugs, 1915-1918 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
  - Elections, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 11 / 9-16)
  - Elevators and warehouses, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 11 / 17)
  - Extradition (general), 1908-1921 (Box-folder 11 / 18)
  - Extradition: Arizona, California, 1918-1922 (Box-folder 11 / 19-21)
  - Extradition: California-Oklahoma, 1919-1924 (Box-folder 12 / 1-19)
  - Extradition: Oregon-Wyoming; Canada, 1919-1924 (Box-folder 13 / 1-17)
  - Farm loan applications, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 14 / 1-4)
  - Fees, 1917-1921 (Box-folder 14 / 5-6)
  - Fences, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 7)
  - Ferguson vs. Sobrak, 1921 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
  - Firearms; guns, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 9)
  - First National Bank of Billings, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 14 / 10)
  - First National Bank of Minneapolis vs. Johnson, 1926 (Box-folder 14 / 11)
  - First Trust and Savings Bank of Billings, 1910 (Box-folder 14 / 12)
  - Fitzgerald case, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 14 / 13)
  - Food and Fuel Administration, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 14)
  - Forestry, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 14 / 15)
  - Forms (for various purposes and various agencies), 1906-1919 (Box-folder 14 / 16-29)
  - Gambling, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 14 / 30-32)
  - Game Laws (re hunting), 1908-1920 (Box-folder 14 / 33-34)
  - Gergen vs. State Board of Hail Insurance, 1925 (Box-folder 14 / 35)
  - Golden Valley County investigation, 1924 (Box-folder 14 / 36)
  - Guettler vs. Bjornsgaard, 1927 (Box-folder 14 / 37)
  - Habeas Corpus, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 14 / 38)
  - Harrison Fraternal Society, 1916-1917 (Box-folder 14 / 39)
  - Hennepin Mortgage Company vs. State, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 14 / 40)
  - Hewett State Bank (Basin, Mont.), 1910-1911 (Box-folder 14 / 41)
  - Hibbard vs Nixon, 1927 (Box-folder 14 / 42)
  - Hibbard vs McGraw, 1927 (Box-folder 14 / 43)
  - Hicks vs. Stillwater County, 1928 (Box-folder 14 / 44)
  - Homesteads, 1910-1916 (Box-folder 14 / 45)
  - Home Savings and State Bank vs. Lindstrom, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 14 / 46)
  - Horses, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 14 / 47)
  - Immigration, 1909 (Box-folder 14 / 48)
  - Indians, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 14 / 49)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (IWW), 1918 (Box-folder 14 / 50)
  - Inheritance tax, 1911-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 51-52)
  - Insurance, 1911-1918 (Box-folder 14 / 53)
  - Insurance, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 1-2)
  - Intermountain Auto Service Club, 1926 (Box-folder 15 / 3)
  - Investigations, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 4)
  - Irrigation, 1915-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 5)
  - Islands, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 6)
  - Italian nationals, 1910 (Box-folder 15 / 7)
  - Itinerant vendors, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 15 / 8)
  - Judiciary, 1909 (Box-folder 15 / 9)
  - Judson, George A. (Box-folder 15 / 10)
  - Jurors, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 11)
  - Justice of the Peace, 1910-1919 (Box-folder 15 / 12)
  - Kibbe vs. Bitter Root Irrigation District, 1923 (Box-folder 15 / 13)
  - Labor, 1913-1915 (Box-folder 15 / 14)
  - Land matters, 1906-1918 (Box-folder 15 / 15)
  - Law Enforcement investigations, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 15 / 16)
  - Laws, 1908-1911, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 17-22)
  - Legislation, 1910-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 23-26)
  - Levine, Louis, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 15 / 27)
  - Licenses, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 15 / 28)
  - Licenses, 1908-1913 (Box-folder 16 / 1-2)
  - Liquor and liquor licenses, 1912-1921 (Box-folder 16 / 3-10)
  - Livestock and Livestock Board, 1915-1921 (Box-folder 16 / 11-12)
  - Loan applications, farm, 1917 (Box-folder 16 / 13-20)
  - Lottery, 1912 (Box-folder 16 / 21)
  - McLeod vs. Mercer, 1925 (Box-folder 16 / 22)
  - McNair estate, 1925 (Box-folder 16 / 23)
  - Marriage, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 16 / 24)
  - Martin incident (Big Timber), 1918 (Box-folder 16 / 25)
  - Meagher, Thomas Francis (re death), 1913 (Box-folder 16 / 26)
  - Medicine, 1913-1920 (Box-folder 16 / 27)
  - Mid-canyon wreck (re railroad accident), 1909 (Box-folder 16 / 28)
  - Middlewest Securities Company vs. State, 1921 (Box-folder 16 / 29)
  - Midland National Bank of Billings vs. Yellowstone County, 1926 (Box-folder 16 / 30)
  - Military, 1914-1916 (Box-folder 16 / 31)
  - Military, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 1-2)
  - Mineral County case, 1918 (Box-folder 17 / 3)
  - Mineral reservation, 1924 (Box-folder 17 / 4)
  - Mines and mining, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 5)
  - Montana, Wyoming and Southern Railway Company, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 17 / 6)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1918 (Box-folder 17 / 7)
  - Montana. boards (miscellaneous), 1916-1919 (Box-folder 17 / 8)
  - Montana. Boiler Inspector, 1909-1916 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
  - Montana. Carey Land Act Board, 1909-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 10-12)
  - Montana. Council of Defense, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 13)
  - Montana. Dairy Commission, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 14)
  - Montana. Deaf and Blind School, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 17 / 15)
  - Montana. Examiner, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 16)
  - Montana. Fair, 1912-1919 (Box-folder 17 / 17)
  - Montana. Fire Marshal, 1911-1917 (Box-folder 17 / 18)
  - Montana. Fish Hatcheries, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 19)
  - Montana. Governor, 1911-1919 (Box-folder 17 / 20)
  - Montana. Grain Inspector, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 17 / 21)
  - Montana. Hail Insurance Board, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 22)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 23)
  - Montana. Historical Library, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 17 / 24)
  - Montana. Horticultural Board, 1911-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 25)
  - Montana. Hospital for the Insane, 1909-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 26-29)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 17 / 30)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys, 1918 (Box-folder 17 / 31)
  - Montana. Land Dept., 1907-1912 (Box-folder 17 / 32-35)
  - Montana. Land Dept., 1912-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 1-7)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 18 / 8)
  - Montana. Optometry Examiners Board, 1913-1916 (Box-folder 18 / 9)
  - Montana. Orphans Home, 1911-1918 (Box-folder 18 / 10)
  - Montana. Osteopathic Examiners Board, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 11)
  - Montana. Prison, 1907-1917 (Box-folder 18 / 12)
  - Montana. Public Health Dept., 1914-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 13-14)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission; Public Service Commission, 1916-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 15-16)
  - Montana. School for the Deaf and Blind, 1913-1918 (Box-folder 18 / 17)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1913-1918 (Box-folder 18 / 18)
  - Montana. Soldiers' Home, 1912-1915 (Box-folder 18 / 19)
  - Montana. Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1911-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 20)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Hospital, 1911-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 21-22)
  - Montana. University System, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 23)
  - Montana. (misc. reports of agencies), 1905-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 24)
  - Mortgages, 1912-1921 (Box-folder 19 / 1-2)
  - Moving pictures (movies), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 19 / 3)
  - Naturalization, 1916-1920 (Box-folder 19 / 4)
  - Navigation, 1909 (Box-folder 19 / 5)
  - Negroes, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 19 / 6)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1926 (Box-folder 19 / 7)
  - Norton estate, 1925 (Box-folder 19 / 8)
  - Notary Public, 1909-1920 (Box-folder 19 / 9)
  - Nurses, 1913-1916 (Box-folder 19 / 10)
  - Office supplies, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 19 / 11)
  - Opinions, 1913-1921 (Box-folder 19 / 12)
  - Pardons, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 19 / 13)
  - Parole investigations, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 19 / 14)
  - Paroles, 1908-1913 (Box-folder 19 / 15)
  - Paroles: denied and granted, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 19 / 16-17)
  - Payrolls and claims, 1925-1933 (Box-folder 19 / 18-20)
  - Peddlers, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 19 / 21)
  - Pensions, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 19 / 22)
  - Personal: Sam C. Ford, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 19 / 23-25)
  - Police, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 19 / 26)
  - Politics, 1920 (Box-folder 19 / 27)
  - Premiums, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 19 / 28)
  - Printing, Public, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 19 / 29)
  - Printing, 1912-1920 (Box-folder 19 / 30)
  - Prisoners, 1908-1921 (Box-folder 19 / 31-34)
  - Prisoners on roads (chain gangs?), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 20 / 1)
  - Prohibition, 1919 (Box-folder 20 / 2)
  - Prostitution, 1917 (Box-folder 20 / 3)
  - Prostitution: Havre, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 20 / 4)
  - Race Track Creek power site, 1909-1913 (Box-folder 20 / 5)
  - Radigan vs. Brandjord, 1925 (Box-folder 20 / 6)
  - Railroads, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 20 / 7)
  - Rape, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 20 / 8)
  - Reform School, 1914-1918 (Box-folder 20 / 9)
  - Registration, 1917 (Box-folder 20 / 10)
  - Reports and opinions, 1909-1918 (Box-folder 20 / 11-12)
  - Requests for information, 1910-1913 (Box-folder 20 / 13-25)
  - Requests for information, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 21 / 1-24)
  - Requests for opinion, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 21 / 25-28)
  - Requests for opinion, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 22 / 1-15)
  - Resignations, 1907-1921 (Box-folder 22 / 16)
  - Restoration to citizenship of convicts, 1910-1916 (Box-folder 22 / 17)
  - Revenue, 1914-1918 (Box-folder 22 / 18)
  - Rewards (Northern Pacific train robbery), 1909 (Box-folder 22 / 19)
  - Roads, 1909-1920 (Box-folder 22 / 20-23)
  - Rocky Mountain Fire Insurance Company vs. Bernier, 1926 (Box-folder 22 / 24)
  - Salaries, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 22 / 25)
  - Saloons (re liquor), 1909-1910 (Box-folder 22 / 26)
  - School bonds, 1912-1917 (Box-folder 22 / 27-28)
  - School bonds, 1917-1921 (Box-folder 23 / 1-4)
  - School bonds: transcripts of proceedings, 1917 (Box-folder 23 / 5-7)
  - School census, 1910, 1912 (Box-folder 23 / 8)
  - School districts, 1908-1910 (Box-folder 23 / 9)
  - School trustees, 1911-1920 (Box-folder 23 / 10)
  - Schools, 1915-1920 (Box-folder 23 / 11-16)
  - Sedition, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 23 / 17)
  - Seeds, 1913-1920 (Box-folder 23 / 18-19)
  - Sheep (trespass of), 1910 (Box-folder 23 / 20)
  - Sheriffs, 1914-1920 (Box-folder 23 / 21)
  - Sixteen Hour Law, 1907-1910 (Box-folder 23 / 22)
  - Smith Monument, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 24 / 1)
  - Staats, J.L., disbarment, 1926 (Box-folder 24 / 2)
  - Stallions, 1912-1917 (Box-folder 24 / 3)
  - State Savings Bank, Butte, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 24 / 4)
  - Station at Monida (personal matter), 1910-1908 (Box-folder 24 / 5)
  - Taxation, 1907-1920 (Box-folder 24 / 6-11)
  - Teachers, 1913-1920 (Box-folder 24 / 12)
  - B.S. Thresher case, 1909 (Box-folder 24 / 13)
  - Train robberies, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 24 / 14)
  - Transportation, 1908-1914 (Box-folder 24 / 15)
  - Trespass, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 24 / 16)
  - U.S. vs. Pederson and Renolds, 1924 (Box-folder 24 / 17)
  - U.S. vs. Jerome P. Magee, et al., 1920 (Box-folder 24 / 18)
  - Vacancies, 1911-1916 (Box-folder 24 / 19)
  - Veterinary, 1908-1917 (Box-folder 24 / 20)
  - Voters, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 24 / 21)
  - Warrants, 1910, 1917 (Box-folder 24 / 22)
  - Washington trip, 1911 (Box-folder 24 / 23)
  - Water, 1908-1920 (Box-folder 24 / 24)
  - Weights and measures, 1914-1921 (Box-folder 24 / 25)
  - White Slave Law, 1914 (Box-folder 24 / 26)
  - Wholesale boycott, 1920 (Box-folder 24 / 27)
  - Wise vs. Reum, State, et al., 1924 (Box-folder 24 / 28)
  - Witness, 1910 (Box-folder 24 / 29)
  - Women, 1909-1920 (Box-folder 24 / 30)
  - Young's Point wreck (railroad accident), 1908-1909 (Box-folder 24 / 31)
  - Abstracts, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 32)
  - Admission to Bar, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 33)
  - Application for position, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 34)
  - Appointment, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 35)
  - Appropriations, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 36)
  - Automobiles, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 37)
  - Banks, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 38-40)
  - Blue Sky Law, 1925 (Box-folder 24 / 41)
  - Bonds, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 42-45)
  - Bonus, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 46)
  - Bounty claims, 1925 (Box-folder 24 / 47)
  - Bridges, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 48)
  - Certificates, 1925 (Box-folder 24 / 49)
  - Children, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24 / 50)
  - Cities and towns, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 1)
  - Civil cases, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 2-4)
  - Claims, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 5-6)
  - Clerks of Courts, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 7)
  - Collections, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 8)
  - Compensation, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 9)
  - Complaints, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 10-19)
  - Contracts, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 20)
  - Corporations, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 21)
  - Counties, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 22)
  - County Assessors, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 23)
  - County Attorneys, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 24)
  - County Clerks, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 25)
  - County Commissioners, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 26)
  - County Treasurers, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 27)
  - Criminal cases, 1925 (Box-folder 25 / 28-29)
  - Dairy Commissioner, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 30)
  - Dentistry, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 31)
  - Deputies, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 32)
  - Disbarment, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 33)
  - District Court Judges, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 34)
  - Divorce, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 35)
  - Elections, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 36-37)
  - Elevators, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 38)
  - Escheated estates, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 39)
  - Estates, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 40)
  - Extradition, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 25 / 41)
  - Fees, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 1)
  - Fences, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 2)
  - Firearms (guns), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 3)
  - Fish Hatchery, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 4)
  - Form letters, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 5)
  - Gambling, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 6)
  - Game laws (re hunting and fishing), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 7)
  - Guardianship, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 8)
  - Habeas Corpus, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 9)
  - Homesteads, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 10)
  - Indians, 1924-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 11)
  - Insane patients, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 12)
  - Insurance, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 13)
  - Investigations, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 14)
  - Irrigation, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 15)
  - Jurors, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 16)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 17)
  - Land, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 18)
  - Law violations, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 19-20)
  - Laws and legislation, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 21-23)
  - Letter opinions, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 24-25)
  - Licenses, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 26)
  - Livestock, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 27)
  - Marriage, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 28)
  - Medicine, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 29)
  - Mining, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 30)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 31)
  - Montana. Carey Land Act Board, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 32)
  - Montana. Chiropractic Examiners Board, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 33)
  - Montana. Forester, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 34)
  - Montana. Governor, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 35)
  - Montana. Hail Insurance Board, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 36)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 37)
  - Montana. Land Department, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 38)
  - Montana. Orphan's Home, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 39)
  - Montana. Railroad Commissioners, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 40)
  - Montana. Warm Springs State Hospital, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 41)
  - Mortgages, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 42)
  - Motor transportation, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 43)
  - Naturalization, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 44)
  - Notary Public, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 45)
  - Nurses, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 46)
  - Oil, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 47)
  - Optometry, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 48)
  - Osteopathy, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 49)
  - Pardons and paroles, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 50)
  - Pensions, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 51)
  - Personal, 1925 (Box-folder 26 / 52)
  - Printing, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 53)
  - Prisoners, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 54)
  - Public Service Commissioners, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 55)
  - Rate discrimination, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 56)
  - Recommendations, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 57)
  - Requests for information, 1926 (Box-folder 26 / 58)
  - Reports, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 26 / 59)
  - Opinions, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 26 / 59a)